I don't know if it's recording is it WR
is this thing on is this thing on it's
always hard to know all right so
somebody asked me how I jump started the
car so I thought I'd make a quick video
to show you the device I'll put this in
the Amazon Affiliates link this is not
because I want to sell you something
this is because people were asking so
this is the
device uh it's a jump starter that you
can recharge it's got a light on there
and I actually have a jackary
here's the case it comes in oops here we
go um it comes with it comes with this
look again I'm not selling you this is
not me being like Home Shopping Network
okay I'm just somebody wanted to know so
so here you go it's got the jumper
cables it's got this thing and it goes
in here and then you just jump just like
anything it has like a little indicator
on it how much charge you have you push
the light shows you how much charge it's
got on it
um if you have something like a jackary
to recharge you can actually charge it
and do it multiple times if it doesn't
work the first time I I know from
experience that it doesn't
work uh sometimes it doesn't work and
you have to kind of keep going at it
eventually it will work but sometimes
you have to like recharge the whole
thing to get it to get it to give you
another booster charge um but it's it's
perfect for keeping in the car in an
emergency my wife actually got it for me
um she lived in a I mean she was having
problem with her Subaru Baja for a while
and so she kept that she kept that in
her car um having that charged up is
really nice especially if you are on the
road like I am so much so that's the
thing so I hope that answer your
question Ronnie and